autonomous.ai 2017-11-20

# Privacy | Autonomous

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information that Autonomous. ("we" or "us") collects and how we use that information. This policy is effective 10/1/2013.

##### Your Personal Information

Autonomous is the owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or rent this information, nor will we share it in ways that aren't disclosed in this statement without your consent.

##### Cookies and IP Addresses

Autonomous is firmly committed to customer privacy.

Like many sites, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

We use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to personalize your shopping experience. Cookies are small bits of information collected by your browser and stored in your hard drive. Your browser is usually set up to accept cookies. If you set up your browser to reject cookies, the site will not be able to recognize your cart, your account, or any personal information. We do not and cannot use cookies to gather any confidential information that may be stored on your hard drive.

Autonomous also uses web beacons, which send us cookies that tell us how many times our website has been visited. Third party advertisers also help us display tailored content to our customers. These advertisers may use cookies and/or web beacons to measure the effectiveness of our site. None of the information that is collected by our third party advertisers through their cookies/web beacons will be linked to any personalized information that Autonomous has collected from its members.

##### External Links

This site contains links to other web sites. Autonomous is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.

##### Address Information

Members who request information, products, and services must fill out an order form on our website. We collect your contact information, which includes but is not limited to your home address, email address, phone number, and financial information. Collected information is used for billing, troubleshooting, and sending you information about our company. In some cases, it may be shared with our partners and used to send you their promotional materials. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor your user experience by showing you content you may be interested in (and display it according to your preferences). Customer information is considered to be an asset of Autonomous.

##### Security

To prevent unauthorized access, promote data security, and encourage appropriate use of information, we use a variety of tools (encryption technologies, passwords, physical and electronic security, and procedural safeguards) to protect your information. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the internet, so we make no guarantees.

##### Notification of Changes

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on our website. In the event of amendment, all terms shall become effective 30 days after they are initially posted to the site. Your continued use of Autonomous.ai services will constitute your acceptance of any changes or additions to this Privacy Policy.
